geteducated.com 2017-06-11

# Privacy Policy | GetEducated

GetEducated.com, an Approved Colleges, LLC property is committed to your privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of any information shared with us.

**Information Collected by GetEducated.com:  **

GetEducated.com collects various types of information to help you provide contact information to colleges and universities available on our website. 

Information we collect and store may include:

  * First and last name
  * Phone number
  * Mailing address
  * Email address
  * General demographic information such as age
  * Preferences and education information
  * Search and browse information

Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies or other tracking technologies. The type of information your browser or Internet session may automatically provide us with can include the browser you are using, your Internet domain, the operating system on your computer, your IP address and the URL you saw just before coming to GetEducated.com and, the pages you saw while on our site.

From time to time we may contract with third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may also use cookies or other measures to collect your non-personally identifiable information. GetEducated.com or our partners collect information that you may to provide when requesting additional information from colleges and universities such as name, address, and email address.

**How Your Information May Be Used:   **

The non-personally identifiable information that GetEducated.com collects is used internally for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals. 

Examples of ways in which your information may be used:

  * Sending collected information to schools or institutions that consumers indicate as interests.
  * Compiling and sending newsletters or other marketing materials to the consumer.
  * Organizing information into relevant and meaningful data packages for research or evaluation purposes.

If you elect to provide GetEducated.com with personally identifiable information, we may utilize such information for marketing purposes, and this use may result in follow-up communications from GetEducated.com and from our clients. In addition, that information may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to your preferences and behaviors, and for other GetEducated.com sales and marketing efforts. 

All personally identifiable information you choose to provide will be maintained in confidence by GetEducated.com. There are instances, however, when your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information may be shared with third parties, as described below. Your non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of GetEducated.com on an anonymous basis. 

**How and when does GetEducated.com  share user information?**

  * Information is shared when a consumer requests that their information be shared with a school to be contacted.
  * When a user has agreed to be contacted for marketing purposes such as newsletters and or calls among others.
  * In the event that a consumer is affiliated with a business or organization with partnership to GetEducated.com, we may divulge consumer information to their organization upon specific request.
  * In situations where a partnership or arrangement with GetEducated.com creates a business environment where access to user information is necessary, some limited data may be divulged.

When you request information from GetEducatd.com or one or more of our clients, we may transfer that information within GetEducated.com or route your information to our client(s), across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world, so that they may provide the information on their product or service that you requested. 

We may also disclose information to a third party who provides substantially similar services as the original service about which you requested more information. In such situations, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of such sharing. Please be aware that GetEducated.com is very careful in selecting companies with whom it does business. 

In addition to the above situations where your information may be shared with others, there is also the possibility that GetEducated.com, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. In the event of such transaction, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to all collected personally identifiable information. Finally, GetEducated.com may share your information as necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials. 

Wherever your personally identifiable information may be held within GetEducated.com or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the information you shared with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Please note that while GetEducated.com will make every reasonable effort to protect your information, no transmission of data over the Internet is 100% secure. 

Some of our web sites utilize cookies to collect information about your website activities and to recall the personal information you previously shared with us. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

**Credit Card and E-Commerce Policy:**

GetEducated.com does not collect or store credit card information. Our transactions that utilize credit cards are carried out through Authorize.net, a third-party Visa company. For additional information regarding Authorize.net visit their privacy policy here: <http://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/> 

**User Rights and Abilities Regarding Information Sharing:**

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting GetEducated.com web sites. 

You may choose whether or not to provide personally identifiable information to GetEducated.com. If you choose to provide such information to GetEducated.com, you have the right to tell us not to make some of the uses of such information described herein or may have such information deleted in its entirety. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, surveys or promotional communications via email, you may opt-out by clicking here and following the instructions to unsubscribe. To have your personal information completely removed from our databases, simply contact us at Privacy@GetEducated.com and provide the name of the service for which information was provided, your full name, mailing address, phone number and email address so that we may identify you in the opt-out process. Once we receive your instruction, we will promptly take corrective action. 

**Additional Rights Include:**

  * A user may opt to stop receiving marketing materials and promotional email, direct mail or phone calls at their own discretion.
  * A user may wish to update their information with GetEducated.com to ensure accuracy.
  * A user may request the removal of their data from GetEducated.com systems at any time though this action may not effect actions taken prior to the request being made in some cases.

**Outbound Links and Third-Party Sites:**

Within GetEducated.com the user may encounter links to resources, pages and sites that are independent of GetEducated.com. GetEducated.com makes every reasonable effort to only provide outbound links that are both safe and of value to the user but cannot guarantee what the user may experience on third-party sites. If a user experiences a conflict or poor experience due to a link followed on GetEducated.com we encourage you to contact us immediately.

To the extent that you do provide us with personally identifiable information, GetEducated.com wishes to maintain the accuracy of this information. Where we collect personally identifiable information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting GetEducated.com should you need to update or correct that information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your personally identifiable information to privacy@GetEducated.com and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in the information that we hold as soon as practicable. 

GetEducated.com is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. 

**Information Security:**

We take every available security measure to protect the confidentiality of personal information under our control and appropriately limit access to it. Any information transmitted through GetEducated.com is done so at the users own risk and GetEducated.com does not make any guarantee regarding the data that is sent. The following outlines our current security practices and procedures:

We use a variety of information security measures to protect your online transactions with us. The GetEducated.com store uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL protects information you submit via our websites such as ordering information, including your name, address and credit card number.

GetEducated.com does not store sensitive data such as, credit card numbers and social security numbers on our servers. We use a secure third party gateway through the services of Authorize.net, CyberSource.

CyberSource is committed to privacy and security. CyberSource is compliant with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard ("PCI DSS") as a Level 1 service provider. CyberSource has been compliant with PCI DSS since its inception in 2002. PCI DSS is the bankcard industry's most stringent security standard. Examples of CyberSource's security measures include: physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards; sophisticated security monitoring tools; documented security policies; use of strong encryption for transmissions of Order Information to and from CyberSource Customers; restricting access to personally identifiable information; and, periodic security audits by third party security experts.<http://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/>

**Terms of Use:**

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to GetEducated.com's processing of personally identifiable information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy. 

**Privacy Policy Updates:**

From time to time we may need to make changes to our privacy policy to reflect changes in our business, practices or environment. In situations where changes are significant a notification will be posted on our site.

**Contact Us:**

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding ApprovedColleges.com's Privacy Policy, you may email us at [privacy@GetEducated.com](mailto:privacy@approvedcolleges.com) or call us at 1-888-972-7937.

**GetEducated.com; Approved Colleges, LLC Extension Policy (not applicable for IT courses)**

It is required that all student extensions be requested prior to the cessation of the student’s enrollment period. Students have a thirty (30) day grace period after their course enrollment lapses to request an extension of the course.

If a student is beyond their course cessation date by thirty-one (31) days or more, there will be no extension and the purchase of a new course will be required.

No course or series of courses can be extended by more than one (1) year. 

Approved Colleges, LLC Course Extension Fees  (not applicable for IT courses)

  * 1 month Extension = $35
  * 3 Month Extension = $105.00 
  * 6 Month Extension = $210.00 
  * 12 Month Extension = $420.00 

**GetEducated.com; Approved Colleges, LLC IT Course Extension Policy**

All extensions for IT courses must be made prior to the cessation of the student’s enrollment date.

IT students will only be granted one (1) three (3) month extension. After that they will be required to purchase a new course. The e-Book library is NOT included with the extension. 

ED4Online IT Course Extension Fees

  * 3 month Extension = $110

**Online  Course Refund Policy    **

Students who register for a training course occasionally change their mind for one reason or another. Regardless of the reason, we believe there should be a definite refund policy for students who decide not to take the course. Refunds for online courses are only given under the following circumstances: 

The student/user did not access any portion of the online course AND the student/user requests a refund, in writing via email sent to GetEducated.com (contact: [here](http://www.approvedcolleges.com/contact)) within three business days from the date of the registration (email notification sent). There will be no refunds for any online courses (or curricula) once a course has been accessed in any manner.   

A full refund will be issued less an administrative fee of $100.

All shipped course materials (books, study guides, CDs, Self-Study Kits, Videos, etc.) are returned, unopened/unused at your own expense if you accept delivery of the package. There are no refunds for Kindle books or e-books.

Additional restocking and shipping costs may apply to returned books.    

Please understand that with the enrollment and accessing of your online course, you have read and agree to the aformentioned refund policy. There are no extensions granted for your course. If you do not complete your course by the end date on your welcome letter, there will be additional fees for extended access.
